bevomedia.com 2013-04-30

# The Bevo Media Exchange - The Performance Marketing Exchange For Affiliate Marketing

BevoMedia, LLC (' **BevoMedia** ') is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of BevoMedia's website (the ' **Website** ') and the services available through the website (the ' **Services** '). BevoMedia created this Privacy Policy to give you (' **You** ' or ' **Your** ') confidence as You visit and use the Website, and to demonstrate its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy.

The Website is linked with the websites of third parties (' **Third-Party Websites** '). This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Website and not to any Third-Party Websites, which may have data collection, storage and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see the section concerning Third-Party Websites, below.

BY USING THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES, YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD, AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF, THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.

Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. For additional information, see the section concerning Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy, below.

  1. ### INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

**Traffic Data.** Like most website operators, BevoMedia automatically gathers information of the sort that browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) domain servers; (iii) types of computers accessing the Website; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Website (collectively ' **Traffic Data** '). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify You. 

**Cookies.** A ' **Cookie** ' is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user submits a query to the website. The purpose of a Cookie is to identify the user as a unique user of the Website. BevoMedia uses Cookies to customize Your experience on the Website to Your interests, to ensure that You do not see the same advertisements or informational messages repeatedly, and to store Your password so You do not have to re-enter it each time You visit the Website. For additional information on BevoMedia' uses of Cookies, see the section concerning Information Use and Disclosure Practices/Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies, below. 

IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER, YOU SHOULD SET YOUR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN OF THE SERVICES AND CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. IF YOU REFUSE COOKIES, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY. 

**Personal Information.** In order for You to use certain of the Services, You may be asked to provide BevoMedia certain information that personally identifies You (' **Personal Information** '). Personal Information includes, without limitation: (1) ' **Contact Data** ' (such as Your name, company name, email address, mailing address, phone number and instant messenger handle); (2) ' **Login Information** ' (such as Your user name and password of Your affiliate/marketing accounts that you wish to view using the Website and Services); and (3) ' **Demographic Data** ' (such as Your instant messenger service, primary website, marketing method, zip code and country). In each case, You will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Website will not gather it surreptitiously. BevoMedia may supplement the Personal Information You provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third-parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide such information to BevoMedia. 

You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that Your refusal to do so may prevent You from using certain of the Services. 

  2. ### INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE PRACTICES

**Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies** BevoMedia analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help BevoMedia better understand who is using the Website and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, BevoMedia is able to better design the Website to improve Your experience, and to serve You more relevant and interesting content and advertisements. From time to time, BevoMedia may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. BevoMedia does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information. 

**Personal Information**

**Generally.** BevoMedia uses Your Contact Data to send You information about BevoMedia and BevoMedia' products and services and to contact You when necessary in connection with the Services. BevoMedia uses Your Login Information to provide the Services. BevoMedia uses Your Demographic Data to customize and tailor Your experience on the Website. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time BevoMedia may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Website. 

**Disclosure Practices**

Except under the following circumstances, BevoMedia will keep Your Personal Information private, and will not share it with third parties. 

**Disclosure in Connection with Services.** BevoMedia discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide Services, including those who perform technical, administrative and data processing tasks such as hosting, data storage and security. 

**By Law or to Protect Rights.** BevoMedia discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when BevoMedia believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of BevoMedia, third parties or the public at large. 

**Business Transfers; Bankruptcy.** BevoMedia reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of BevoMedia' assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if You are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt-out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by BevoMedia successor organization. 

  3. ### SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

BevoMedia has implemented and maintains reasonable security procedures and practices to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction or disclosure of Your Personal Information. 

  4. ### USER ABILITY TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

You must promptly notify us if Your user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. In such and event, we will remove that user name or password from Your account and updated our records accordingly. 

  5. ### LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION

**BevoMedia wants Your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. You represent and warrant that all information You provide on any registration form or otherwise in connection with Your use of the Website and Services will be complete and accurate, and that You will update that information as necessary to maintain its completeness and accuracy. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, Your Personal Information, visit Your personal profile. Through Your personal profile You may review and update You Personal Information that we have already collected.**

  6. ### THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

BevoMedia neither owns nor controls Third-Party Websites. Accordingly, Third-Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by BevoMedia. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to a Third-Party Website, You should inform Yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of that Third-Party Website, and should take those steps necessary to, in Your discretion, protect Your privacy. 

  7. ### SURVEYS

From time to time, BevoMedia may also ask You to participate in surveys designed to help BevoMedia improve the Websites or Services. Any Personal Information provided to BevoMedia in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form. 

  8. ### UPDATES AND CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

Although most changes are likely to be minor, BevoMedia reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such update, change or modification on this page. Any such addition, update, change or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. Each time You use the Website, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, each time You use the Website You should check the date of this Privacy Policy (which appears at the end) and review any changes since the last time You used the Website. Unless BevoMedia obtains Your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of such revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy. 

Effective Date: [January 1st, 2010]
